Guide to the J. Walter Thompson Company. 35mm Microfilm Proofs, 1906-1960 and undated
The John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library Duke University Durham, N.C., USA
- Accounts, 1906-1941 and undated
  - Charles William Co. (stores), 1914
  - Wood Associates (office furniture), 1930
  - Wm. Wrigley (chewing gum), 1931-1934
- Foreign Proofs Previous to 1934
  - Alexandria (Egypt) (Reel 41)
    - Quaker Oats
    - Shelltox
    - Peak Prean
    - Jantzen
    - Victor
    - Gillette
    - Dollar Line
    - General Motors
      - Chevrolet trucks
      - Chevrolet passenger cars
      - Buick
      - Institutional
  - Antwerp (Belgium)
    - General Motors
      - Chevrolet
      - Pontiac
      - Buick--Marquette
      - Blity truck
      - Complete line
    - Victor
    - Zoo candies
    - De Kuyper's liqueurs
    - Eastman Kodak
    - Fyffe's bananas
    - Felix cat food
    - Flexo watch crystals
    - Frigidaire
    - Gillette
    - Carpal
    - CeCo radio tubes
    - Chile saltpetre
    - Coca-Cola
    - Goodrich
    - Victor
    - Jantzen
    - Johnson Sea Horses
    - Kraft
    - Extrait de Viande Liebig
    - Cutex
    - De Beukelaer
  - Batavia (Java)
    - General Motors
      - Buick
      - Cadillac
    - Johnson Sea Horses
    - Eastman Kodak
    - Goodrich
  - Berlin (Germany)
    - Johnson Sea Horses
    - General Motors
      - Chevrolet trucks
      - Chevrolet passenger cars
      - Marquette
      - Oakland
      - Oldsmobile
      - Pontiac
      - Vauxhall
    - Acrophon
    - Bakelite
    - Chile saltpetre
    - Coca-Cola
    - Eastman Kodak
    - Electrola
    - Gillette
    - Goodrich
    - Victor
    - Alpine--Gruen watches
    - Horlicks
    - Jantzen
    - Kraft
    - Pond's
    - Quaker Oats
    - Blondex
    - Royal baking powder
    - Sun Maid raisins
    - Sagrotan
  - Bombay (Mumbai, India)
    - General Motors
      - Buick
      - Chevrolet trucks
      - Chevrolet passenger cars
      - Vauxhall
      - Pontiac
      - Opel
      - GMC
    - Wotto Brady & Co. Ltd
    - Eastman Kodak
    - Edsu fabrics
    - Goodrich
    - Horlicks
    - Johnson & Johnson
    - Royal baking powder
    - Scott's Emulsion
    - Silk Flakes
    - Tata Oil Mills Co., Ltd.
      - 501 soap
      - Cocogem
      - Tej boot polish
      - Challak motor polish
    - Mobil Oil
  - Bucharest (Romania/Rumania)
    - General Motors
      - Opel
    - Eastman Kodak
    - Gilbert & Parker
    - Goodyear
    - Columbia Records
    - Pond's
    - Ivanhoe Perfection stove
    - Sare de Lux
    - Standard Oil
    - Prestone
    - Electrogay
    - Telephone Co.
    - Chat Noir & Lady cosmetics
    - Carn cigarettes
  - Buenos Aires (Argentina)
    - General Motors
      - Chevrolet trucks
      - Oakland
      - Pontiac
      - Buick
      - Cadillac
      - Oldsmobile
      - Chevrolet passenger cars
    - Brasso
    - Dunlap
    - Eastman Kodak
    - Frigidaire
    - General Electric
    - Goodrich
    - Modess
    - Karpal
    - National City Bank
    - Nael candies
    - Overseas Motor Service Corp.
      - New Departure
      - Hycoe
      - Delco-Remy
    - Padilla vermouth
    - Pond's
    - Pyrrhocide
    - Royal baking powder
    - Santos cigars
    - Sonora
    - Waldorf tissues
    - Swift's
    - Por Taytoy milk
    - J. Walter Thompson
    - Standard Oil
  - Montreal and Toronto (Canada)
    - Gruen
    - Goodrich
    - Gillette
    - Fleischmann's baking powder
    - Fleischmann's yeast for health
    - Royal yeast cakes
    - Shell Oil
    - J. Walter Thompson
    - Kraft
    - Magic baking powder
    - Libby's
    - Lafayette
    - Windsor Duo towel
    - Chase & Sanborn coffee
    - Clover Leaf salmon
    - Cream of Wheat
    - Cutex
  - Copenhagen (Denmark)
    - General Motors
      - GMC
      - Chevrolet
    - Imi
    - Jantzen
    - Jonarista
    - Odo-ro-no
    - Ota
    - Overseas Motor Service Corp.
      - AC spark plugs
      - Delco-Remy
      - Lonejoy
      - New Departure
      - Hycoe
    - Poma
    - Peder Maller
    - Persil
    - Sun Maid raisins and prunes
    - Ude og Hjemme
    - Westerby
    - Alfa margarine
    - Beech-Nut chewing gum
    - Röda Björn
    - Ceraa
    - Granulerat Chilisaltpeter
    - Cutex
    - Diamant
    - Eastman Kodak
    - Flint & Vaegen
    - Fructus
    - Goetjes Suebakker
    - Gillette
    - Gluten flour
    - Flexo watch crystals
    - Henkil & Co.
  - Johannesburg (South Africa)
    - General Motors
      - Chevrolet trucks
      - Chevrolet passenger cars
      - Marquette
      - Oakland
      - Oldsmobile
      - Opel
      - Pontiac
      - Vauxhall
    - Royal baking powder
    - Murray & Stewart
    - Moir's jellies
    - Menek
    - Karanan
    - Jantzen
    - Horlicks
    - Goodrich
    - Electrolux
    - Cream of Wheat
    - Clubman shoes
    - Black & White scotch
    - Chateau brandy
    - Atlantic Refineries
  - London (England, Great Britain)
    - Pineoleum
    - Odo-ro-no
    - Marconiphone Loudspeaker
    - McVitie & Price Ltd.
    - Lux soap and flakes
    - Horlicks
    - Libby, McNeill & Libby
    - Johnson Sea Horses
    - Jantzen
    - Ideal Hrue Dairies
    - Royal baking powder
    - Sun Maid raisins
    - Swift's
    - Vaseline
    - Eastman Kodak (Cuba)
    - Goodrich
    - Hall's wines
    - Harpic
    - Pond's
    - Pyrex
    - Ramntree's candies
    - Rinso
    - General Motors
      - Vauxhall
      - Buick
      - Chevrolet trucks
      - Chevrolet passenger cars
      - Cadillac
      - LaSalle
      - Marquette
    - Atkinson face powder
    - Beech-Nut chewing gum
    - Bink's paint spray
    - Boot's chemists
    - Frank's Foods
    - Brisling
    - Chileau Nitrate Producers Association, Ltd.
    - L.C. Smith and Corona
    - Cream of Wheat
    - Cutex
    - Courtauldo rayon
  - Madrid (Spain)
    - Hind's
    - Horlicks
    - Jantzen
    - Odo-ro-no
    - Quaker Oats
    - Vicente Rico
    - Victor
    - Royal baking powder
    - Simmon's
    - Coca-Cola
    - Delco-Luy
    - Eastman Kodak
    - Frigidaire
    - Gillette
    - Goodrich
    - General Motors
      - Chevrolet trucks
      - Chevrolet passenger cars
      - Oakland
      - Opel
      - GMC
  - Paris (France)
    - General Motors
      - Buick
      - Chevrolet trucks
      - Chevrolet passenger cars
      - GMC
      - Marquette
      - Oakland
      - Oldsmobile
      - Pontiac
    - Coca-Cola
    - Postal Telegraph
    - Eastman Kodak
    - Gillette
    - Goodrich
    - Victor
    - Jantzen
    - Johnson Sea Horses
    - Libby, McNeill & Libby
    - Quaker Oats
    - Sao Paulo (Brazil)
    - Atlantic Refineries
    - Blue Star Lines
    - Casa Pratt
    - Eastman Kodak
    - Fleischmann's yeast for health
    - Goodrich
    - General Motors
      - Chevrolet trucks
      - Chevrolet passenger cars
    - Oakland
    - Jantzen
    - Johnson Sea Horses
    - Maiyena
    - Duryea
    - Leite Moca
    - RCA tubes
    - Refinacoes de Milbo Brasil
    - Royal baking powder
    - Casa Forte de Sur America
  - Stockholm (Sweden)
    - Combri
    - Cutex
    - DuPont Duco
    - Ditzinger's
    - Victor
    - Layarin
    - Lyon's tea
    - Medital
    - Modehurst
    - Ovaltine
    - General Motors
      - Opel
      - GMC
      - Buick
      - Chevrolet trucks
      - Chevrolet passenger cars
  - Sydney (Australia)
    - Pond's
    - Potter & Moore
    - Spaulding
    - Nujol
    - Flit
    - Mistol
    - Daggett & Rounsdell
    - J. Walter Thompson
    - Matson Lines
    - Lux soap and flakes
    - Kraft
    - Johnson Sea Horses
    - Jantzen
    - Horlicks
    - Chamberlain's cough medicine
    - Australian Bedeaux
    - General Motors
      - Vauxhall
      - Pontiac
      - Oldsmobile
      - Oakland
      - Chevrolet trucks
      - Chevrolet passenger cars
  - Warsaw (Poland)
    - Drazetki Bengalskie
    - Saletra Chilyska
    - Victor
    - Gillette
    - General Motors
      - Pontiac
      - Oldsmobile
      - LaSalle
      - Chevrolet trucks
      - Chevrolet passenger cars
      - Cadillac
      - Buick
  - Wellington (New Zealand)
    - Matson Lines
    - Johnson Sea Horses
    - Horlicks
    - CeCe radio tubes
    - General Motors
      - Bedford trucks
      - Vauxhall
      - Pontiac
      - Chevrolet trucks
      - Chevrolet passenger cars
- Western Office Accounts, 1916-1928 and undated
  - Kraft-Phenix (Reel 42)
  - Libby, McNeill & Libby, 1916-1919
  - Libby, McNeill & Libby, 1919-1928 (continued) (Reel 43)
  - Swift & Co., undated
  - Swift & Co., undated (Reel 44)
  - Swift & Co., undated (Reel 45)
- Copyright material stamped and returned from Washington, undated
  - General Cigar, undated (Reel 45)
  - Pond's, undated
  - Standard Brands, undated
  - Chase & Sanborn, undated
  - Tenderleaf Tea, undated
  - Royal baking powder, undated
  - Royal Gelatin, undated
  - Royal pudding, undated
  - Fleischmann's Yeast for Health, undated
  - Fleischmann's Irradiated Yeast for Animals, undated
- Supplement to 16mm reel 40, 1933-1939
  - Copy approvals
    - Lever Brothers (Lux Toilet Soap) (Reel 46)
      [Dr. Killian, Breed, Abbott & Morgan (advertisements, coupons, leaflets), Dr. Susan scripts, Lux Radio Theatre commercials]
    - General Cigar
      [Special News Events consents, Vintage advertising consents]
    - Pond's
      [Client, Miss Olzendam, Dr. Killian, Dr. Andrews, Dr. Cipallaro, Mr. Clark and Mr. Voorhees (clients' lawyers)--radio commercials]
    - Standard Brands
    - Chase & Sanborn
      [Breed, Abbott & Morgan, Dr. Lee, Dr. Killian, Miss Olzendam/client]
    - Tenderleaf Tea
      [Dr. Lee, Dr. Killian, Miss Olzendam, client]
    - Emerson Drug Co. (Bromo-Seltzer)
    - Lever Brothers (Lux Toilet Soap) (Reel 47)
      [Dr. John Killian--newspapers 1937, magazines 1936-1940]
    - General Cigar
      [White Owl cigars; magazines 1933, 1936]
    - Pond's
      [Magazines; Danya 1937-1938, Vanishing Cream 1938, Cold Cream 1938-1939, Glare Proof powder 1938, Cream Extra Vitamin Skin 1937-1938, Cold Cream Under Skin treatment 1937-1938]
    - Standard Brands
      [magazines; Chase & Sanborn coffee 1938-1939, Bergen cartoons 1937, Dated Coffee 1936]
    - Emerson Drug Co. (Bromo-Seltzer_
      [Magazines 1936-1938]
  - Car cards
    - Lux Flakes (Reel 48)
    - Fleischmann's Stox
    - Pertussin (Seeck & Kade)
    - Charter Oak bread
    - Fleischmann's Stox
    - Fleischmann's Yeast for Health
    - Old Witch
    - O'Sullivan's heels
    - Aunt Jemima pancake flour
  - Newspaper and magazine advertisements
    - Lux toilet soap, undated
    - Lux Flakes, undated
    - Fleischmann's Dry Gin, 1934
    - Chase & Sanborn, 1934-1935
    - Lux Flakes, 1934
    - Lux toilet soap
    - Standard Brands (copyright materials; continued on reel 50), undated (Reel 49)
    - Lucky Strike cigarettes, 1933
    - Chase & Sanborn, 1931-1934
    - CW brand coffee, 1932-1934
    - Royal pudding, 1931-1934
    - Royal Gelatin, 1934
    - Tenderleaf Tea, 1931-1935
    - Royal baking powder, 1931-1934
    - Fleischmann's yeast, 1930-1935
    - Fleischmann's Dry Gin, 1937
    - Chase & Sanborn, 1937
- Portfolios, 1931-1938
  - Standard Brands, Inc.
    - Chase & Sanborn, 1932-1935
    - Royal Gelatin, 1933
    - Chase & Sanborn, 1932
    - Ironized Yeast, 1932
    - Fleischmann's Yeast for Health, 1932
    - Tenderleaf Tea, 1933
    - Potato chips, 1933
    - CW brand coffee, 1932-1935
    - Fleischmann's Yeast for Health, 1935
    - Rinso, 1933 May
    - Lux Flakes, 1933 Mar.
    - Tenderleaf Tea, 1933-1935
    - Lux Flakes
    - C& S Royal vanilla pudding, 1933
  - Newspaper and magazine advertisements
    - Tenderleaf Tea, 1934-1935
    - Royal baking powder, 1934
    - CW brand coffee, 1932
    - Chase & Sanborn, 1932-1933
    - Royal Gelatin, 1935
    - Royal pudding, 1932-1933
    - Royal Gelatin, 1934
    - Tenderleaf Tea, 1932
    - Royal desserts, 1931-1933
    - Tenderleaf Tea, 1935
    - Chase & Sanborn, 1931
    - Royal baking powder, 1931-1935
    - Tenderleaf Tea, 1935
    - Fleischmann's Yeast for Health, 1931-1935
    - Lux Flakes, 1933-1934
    - Zenith radio, 1934 May
    - Chase & Sanborn, 1932
    - Rinso, 1932
    - Lux Flakes, 1931
    - Jergens' lotion, 1937 Nov.
    - Fleischmann's yeast, Life Begins at 40, 1937
  - Standard Brands, Inc.
    - Fleischmann's yeast, Life Begins at 40, 1936 (Reel 50)
    - Royal desserts, undated
    - Fleischmann's Yeast for Health, undated
    - Fleischmann's yeast for animals, 1931
    - Chase & Sanborn, 1937
    - Fleischmann's Dry Gin, 1937
    - Tenderleaf Tea, 1937
    - Rinso, 1937 Mar.
    - Fleischmann's yeast, Arthur Murray, 1937
    - Fleischmann's yeast, Life Begins at 40, 1937
    - Fleischmann's yeast for health, 1938
    - Royal baking powder, 1937
  - White Owl cigars, 1933-1937
  - Standard Brands, Inc.
    - Lux toilet soap, 1934
    - Fleischmann's Yeast XR, 1935
    - Fleischmann's yeast for dogs, 1935
    - Fleischmann's Yeast for health, 1934
    - Royal baking powder, 1934
    - Fleischmann's yeast, 1931-1937
- Proof Portfolios, 1914-1951 and undated
  - American Home Products, 1939-1941 (Reel 51)
  - American Home Products, 1943
  - Astaire, Fred, 1946-1947
  - Block Drug Co., 1942-1944
  - Boston Globe, 1935-1943
  - Buxton, 1924-1941
  - Buxton, 1942-1951 (continued)
  - Carter's Products, 1942-1945 (Reel 52)
  - Chicago Community Fund, 1937
  - City Baking Co., 1923-1934
  - City Baking Co., 1925-1937 (continued)
  - Coordinator of Inter American Affairs, 1943-1945
  - CW brand coffee, 1930-1935
  - Dr. Price baking powder, 1929-1935
  - Fulton Sylphen, 1944-1945
  - General Cigar, 1933-1939 (Reel 53)
  - General Cigar, 1940-1951 (continued)
  - GCMI, 1948
  - Guinness. Arthur & Sons, 1933-1938 (Reel 54)
  - Guinness. Arthur & Sons, 1938-1942 (continued)
  - Guinness. Arthur & Sons, 1943-1948 (continued)
  - Lever-Vimms, 1944-1945
  - Lever-Vimms (trade), 1944
  - Martini & Rossi, 1939-1941 (Reel 55)
  - McFadden Publications, 1939
  - Nashua Manufacturing, 1947-1949
  - Newspapers Publishers Committee, 1940-1941
  - New York Dress Institute, 1940-1943 (Reel 56)
  - New York subways, 1942
  - Northam Warren, 1937-1944
  - Northam Warren (Cutex), 1916-1918 (Reel 57)
  - Northam Warren (Cutex), 1919 (continued)
  - Northam Warren (Cutex), 1920 (continued)
  - Northam Warren (Cutex), 1921-1922 (continued)
  - Northam Warren (Cutex), 1923-1925 (continued)
  - Northam Warren (Cutex), 1926-1927 (continued)
  - Northam Warren (Cutex), 1923-1929 (continued) (Reel 58)
  - Northam Warren (Cutex), 1930 (continued)
  - Northam Warren (Cutex), 1931 (continued)
  - Northam Warren (Cutex), 1932-1933 (continued)
  - Northam Warren (Cutex), 1934-1935 (continued)
  - Northam Warren (Cutex), 1936-1937 (continued)
  - Northam Warren (Cutex), 1938-1940 (continued) (Reel 59)
  - Northam Warren (Cutex), 1941-1943 (continued)
  - Northam Warren (Cutex), 1944-1947 (continued)
  - Odo-ro-no, 1940-1941
  - Old Gold, 1941
  - Old Gold (magazine advertising 1941 on reel 69), 1942
  - OPA-WPA campaigns, 1944
  - Oxford University Press, 1946-1950
  - Pennsylvania Central Airways, 1943-1944 (Reel 60)
  - Pennsylvania Central Airways, 1945 (continued)
  - Petroleum Industry War Council, 1943
  - Planters Nuts & Chocolate Co., 1934-1940
  - Planters Nuts & Chocolate Co., 1943-1944 (continued)
  - Popular Science magazine, 1924-1930
  - Powers, John Robert, 1943-1945
  - Dr. Price baking powder, 1929-1935
  - Quinlan, Kathleen Mary, 1929-1940 (Reel 61)
  - Radio Times, 1937-1940
  - Ready to Serve, 1941
  - Reynolds Metals, 1946-1947
  - Rheem Manufacturing, 1941 (Reel 62)
  - Serfert, 1947-1948
  - Sharp & Dohme, 1930-1931
  - Sharp & Dohme, 1932-1933 (continued)
  - Sharp & Dohme, 1934-1935 (continued)
  - Sharp & Dohme, 1936-1937 (continued)
  - Sharp & Dohme, 1940 (continued)
  - Sharp & Dohme, 1942 (continued) (Reel 63)
  - Sharp & Dohme, 1943-1947 (continued)
  - Standard Brands, Inc.
    - Fleischmann's, 1923-1925
    - Fleischmann's, 1926-1935 (continued)
    - Fleischmann's, 1936-1940 (continued)
    - Fleischmann's, 1941 (continued)
    - Fleischmann's, 1942 (continued)
    - Chase & Sanborn, 1931 (Reel 64)
    - Chase & Sanborn, 1932 (continued)
    - Chase & Sanborn, 1933 (continued)
      [Also potato chips]
    - Chase & Sanborn, 1934 (continued) (Reel 65)
    - Chase & Sanborn, 1935 (continued)
    - Chase & Sanborn, 1936 (continued)
    - Chase & Sanborn, 1936 (continued)
    - Chase & Sanborn, 1937 (continued)
    - Chase & Sanborn, 1938 (continued) (Reel 66)
    - Chase & Sanborn, 1939 (continued)
    - Chase & Sanborn, 1940 (continued)
    - Chase & Sanborn, 1941 (continued)
    - Chase & Sanborn, 1942-1943 (continued) (Reel 67)
    - Chase & Sanborn, 1944 (continued)
    - Chase & Sanborn, 1945 (continued)
    - Chase & Sanborn, 1946 (continued)
    - Chase & Sanborn, 1947 (continued)
    - Chase & Sanborn, 1948 (continued)
    - Chase & Sanborn, 1949 (continued)
  - Taylor, W.A. Co., 1941-1942
  - Textron, 1943-1950 (Reel 68)
  - Todd Shipyards, 1943
  - U.S. Gutta Percha, 1914-1919
  - U.S. Gutta Percha, 1920-1922 (continued)
  - U.S. Gutta Percha, 1923-1926 (continued)
  - U.S. Gutta Percha, 1927-1928 (continued)
  - U.S. Gutta Percha, 1929 (continued)
  - U.S. Gutta Percha, 1930-1931 (continued)
  - U.S. Gutta Percha, 1930-1932 (continued) (Reel 69)
  - U.S. Gutta Percha, 1933-1937 (continued)
  - U.S. Gutta Percha, 1938-1942 (continued)
  - U.S. Navy Relief vol. 1, 1942
  - Western Union Telegraph, 1946-1950
  - Old Gold, 1941
- Portfolio: Inactive Accounts, 1920-1955 and undated
  - Ballantine & Sons, 1935-1941 (Reel 70)
  - Ballantine & Sons, 1941-1946 (continued) (Reel 71)
  - Ballantine & Sons, 1947-1953 (continued) (Reel 72)
  - Ballantine & Sons, 1953-1955 (continued) (Reel 73)
  - Fanny Farmer, 1939-1950 (Reel 74)
  - Florida Citrus, 1950-1955 (Reel 75)
  - New York subways, 1942-1948
  - Penick & Ford, 1920-1943 (Reel 76)
  - Radio Corporation of America (RCA) vol. 1, 1943-1944 (Reel 77)
  - Radio Corporation of America (RCA) vol. 1, 1943-1944 (continued) (Reel 78)
  - National Broadcasting Company, 1945-1946
  - Radio Corporation of America (RCA) America vol. 2, 1947 (Reel 79)
  - Radio Corporation of America (RCA) National vol. 1, 1947 (continued)
  - RCA Victor vol. 1,2, 1947
  - RCA Tube Division, 1947
  - RCA Victor programs vol. 2, 1948 (Reel 80)
  - RCA Victor Division, 1948
  - RCA Engineering Products, 1948
  - RCA programs vol. 1, 1949 (Reel 81)
  - RCA programs vol. 2, 1949
  - RCA American institutional, 1948 (Reel 82)
  - RCA American tube, 1948
  - RCA Engineering Products, 1949
  - RCA institutional, 1949
  - RCA Victor records, 1942
  - RCA home instruments vol. 1, 1949
  - RCA home instruments vol. 2, 1949
  - RCA Victor (4 vol.s), 1950 (Reel 83)
  - RCA Tube Division, 1950 (Reel 84)
  - RCA programs vol. 1, 1950
  - RCA programs vol. 2, 1950
  - RCA American institutional, 1950
  - RCA home instruments, 1953
  - RCA newspaper, undated
  - RCA insertion schedules, 1946 June 24-1947 Dec. 27 (Reel 85)
  - Reynolds Metals, 1943-1945 (Reel 86)
  - Scranton Lace Co., 1943-1947
  - Scranton Lace Co., 1948-1950 (continued)
  - Textron, 1943-1944
  - Document for Pat Nichols, undated
- Portfolios: Discontinued Accounts, 1930-1960 and undated
  - American Cancer Society, 1953-1954 (Reel 87)
  - Aquascutum, 1955-1959
  - Boyle-Midway, 1958-1959
  - Buitoni, 1955-1957
  - Burlington Mills, 1956-1957
  - Carter's Ink, 1931-1947, 1949-1951
  - Church and Dwight, 1949-1959
  - Ciba, 1956-1957
  - Columbia Mills, 1951-1955
  - Crompton, 1957-1958
  - Devoe and Reynolds, 1955-1958 (Reel 88)
  - Farrell Lines, 1949-1959
  - Fieldcrest, 1956-1958
  - Good Housekeeping, 1939-1942
  - E.F. Hutton, 1956
  - Johns-Manville, 1931 Jan.-1933 Jan.
  - Johns-Manville, 1933 June-1938 Nov. (continued) (Reel 89)
  - Johns-Manville, 1938-1942 (continued) (Reel 90)
  - Johns-Manville, 1942-1946 (continued) (Reel 91)
  - Johns-Manville, 1946-1951 (continued) (Reel 92)
  - Johns-Manville, 1951-1957 (continued) (Reel 93)
  - Johns-Manville, 1957-1959 (continued) (Reel 94)
  - New York Central Railroad, 1955-1959
  - Oneida, 1948-1960
  - Pacific Mills, 1956-1957
  - Pacific Mills, 1957-1959 (continued) (Reel 95)
  - Penick & Ford, 1938-1939, 1944-1954
  - Pharmacraft, 1946-1960
  - RCA, 1946
  - Polytravel & Tours, 1955-1960
  - RCA, 1951-1953 (Reel 96)
  - Seth Thomas, 1951-1956
  - Shell Oil, 1932-1935
  - Shell Oil, 1936-1943 (continued) (Reel 97)
    [reel missing as of 4/23/80]
  - Shell Oil, 1942-1951 (continued) (Reel 98)
  - Shell Oil, 1951-1956 (continued) (Reel 99)
  - Shell Oil, 1956-1959 (continued) (Reel 100)
  - Shell Oil, 1959-1960 (continued) (Reel 101)
  - Alexander Smith, 1952-1955
  - Staze, 1950-1955
  - Stouffer, 1958-1960
  - Sylvania, 1955-1956
  - Sylvania, 1956-1959 (continued) (Reel 102)
  - Trico, 1955-1956
  - United Hospital Fund, 1930-1937
  - Ward Baking, 1942-1947
  - Ward Baking, 1947-1949 (continued) (Reel 103)
  - J.B. Williams, 1936-1947
  - J.B. Williams, 1948-1957 (continued) (Reel 104)
  - Wool Bureau, 1954-1960